[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[In my prime]
[Episode 22]
Next week,
Bolly is holding
a distributor investment event.
Are you interested in it?
But whether
you can get the distributorship
all depends on you.
The mere distributorship?
I'll get it for sure.
Here we are.
Here you go, sir.
Alright.
The fare is 20 yuan.
You're 10 short.
I'm not short. You took a detour.
How dare you ask for more money then?
That's a one-way street!
We couldn't get through!
Stop trying to fool me.
One-way street? Seriously?
I get my goods from there every day.
You think I don't know?
Um...
Cut the crap. It's on the meter.
You took a detour. I paid...
How much is it?
Ten yuan!
Don't... Don't pay him.
He took a detour.
There's no time to lose.
Well,
here, 10 yuan for you.
I was not trying to rip him off.
But he took a detour.
He called
Pingchuan Alley a one-way street.
But it's not.
He just took a detour.
We're going to be late.
So many people.
By the time we finish signing in,
it'll be too late.
This way.
Hi, Manager.
You're
such a big shot here?
She was greeting you.
What on earth
is on your mind all day?
Didn't I tell you that?
I just got promoted
to regional operations manager.
I'm a manager, after all.
Hello, Manager.
Hello.
Impressive.
I'm in awe.
It's in there.
Once you go in,
you're on your own.
Give me the umbrella.
Go ahead.
Hello, Ms. Qi.
I've reviewed your application form.
The financial proof section
is blank.
If you become a distributor,
you'll need to pay Bolly
a certain deposit
and advance payment.
Could you provide
your bank statements?
Either corporate
or personal ones will do.
It doesn't need to be much.
A continuous balance
of over 2 million for 6 months
is enough.
I...
I don't have it with me today.
Can I bring it next time?
That's fine.
Ms. Qi,
how many people
are currently in your team?
Twenty.
Well, here's the case, Ms. Qi.
Our team
mainly targets mid-to-high-end customers.
The store requires
professionals in market research,
sales,
customer service,
inventory management,
and so on.
Your team
of 20 people
might not be enough.
Also, Ms. Qi,
may I ask
about the sales revenue
of your team?
What's your annual turnover?
You mean 10 million?
Here's the thing.
If we don't have enough staff,
we can hire more.
The sales revenue isn't high,
but...
But we're
all highly skilled
salespersons.
If
Bolly gives us a chance,
we might deliver results
that exceed expectations.
Bolly can make
any requests.
We will fully cooperate.
Then tell us about
your takes
on Bolly's future brand enhancement
and the expansion
of overseas markets.
Enhancement?
As for overseas markets...
I...
Or,
let's say you've already opened a store.
How do you
plan to make sales?
Just briefly walk us through
your sales plan.
Sales plan...
Or you can think about it...
Production process.
Improve efficiency and quality
and reduce costs.
Well, how about you
redo that data chart?
Got it, Manager.
How did it go?
Did you do this on purpose?
What's wrong?
Your company sets such a high bar.
Why didn't you
make it clear to me?
And you said stores of all sizes
were welcome to apply.
You know
I'm not even qualified to walk
into your company.
I was a total joke in there.
Wait,
what did they ask you?
Is there any misunderstanding?
Manager Cao.
Here's a document
that needs Mr. Li's signature.
Okay.
I'll have him sign it
when he returns this afternoon.
Okay.
So,
it's our first year
carrying out
the regional investment
and ordering system.
But I'm not the one in charge
of the investment.
So I'm also not so sure
what qualification questions
they've prepared.
If their questions
upset you,
I apologize on their behalf.
But don't give up.
There might be
other chances for cooperation.
Cao Xin.
Just a moment.
Mr. Zhang.
Double-check
the decimal points
♪ The wind blew through our hair ♪
in the document.
Make sure the clients review
the materials in advance.
♪ The story slowly gets complicated too ♪
♪ We never became anyone's myth ♪
I'll get on it now.
Okay.
♪ We only learned to grow up in the rain ♪
I'll come get it later.
Okay.
♪ Should we blame fate? ♪
♪ Adulthood is bandaging your own falls ♪
You forgot your umbrella.
Thanks.
♪ Rented rooms, the last bus home ♪
Let me treat you to lunch.
♪ What does the future hold? ♪
There's a Cantonese restaurant
♪ It's been so long since I last
dared to say I was afraid ♪
near our company.
The restaurant near your company
♪ Though we have nothing,
we still bustle about ♪
must be expensive, huh?
Like 300 to 400 yuan per person?
♪ Because the answer is clear
as long as you are around ♪
I can't afford that.
I'm out.
Don't be stubborn.
♪ The old dreams are now covered in dust ♪
♪ But it's okay ♪
If things didn't go smoothly,
let me go over it with you
and see what the problem is.
♪ The morning glow will finally appear ♪
What problem?
It's my problem!
From start to end,
it's just that I don't deserve it.
What happened?
You're barefoot!
Be careful!
♪ Who hasn't panicked
in this fast-paced world? ♪
Shoes!
You're barefoot!
♪ All I see is your gaze ♪
♪ If there's nothing left tomorrow ♪
Sir, sir,
you can just
pull over up ahead.
This is a no-parking zone.
♪ I'll still walk you home ♪
Let me go a bit further to pull over.
This isn't a no-parking zone.
I live around here.
Would I not know
if it's a no-parking zone?
Just pull over right there.
Miss,
I really can't.
I'm the one who gets fined,
not you.
I'll go a bit further
and stop around the corner.
Around the corner?
Alright, here we are.
You have arrived at your destination.
Please pay the amount
shown on the meter.
Make sure
you take your belongings with you.
Alright, be careful.
Miss,
I didn't do anything to you!
What's with the bad attitude?
Keep that up,
and you'll never get a boyfriend.
Who wants a boyfriend?
I want money!
You're back.
Why did you come back barefoot?
I went through all the trouble
to attend a distributor investment event,
only to be mocked
both openly and secretly.
What a lousy day!
You look so mad.
Given our capabilities,
do we even need to attend
the investment event?
Were it not for that nuisance,
I wouldn't have gone!
I even took a cab.
The round trip
wasted me 30 yuan.
We're just not making enough.
I watched the store for you today
and didn't sell
a single piece this morning.
A few customers came in later,
but they just kept trying on the clothes.
It exhausted me.
I thought
I could at least sell a few.
Hasn't it just been like this lately?
Trying on clothes without buying.
Why would they waste time
doing that?
I heard them whispering that
it was cheaper to buy and easier
to return online.
They probably
came here just to try them on
and will buy them online then.
But my prices are also not high.
And I accept returns, too.
But they still have to make
a trip back here to return them.
You know what?
Young people these days
are all lazybones.
They just do whatever takes
the least effort.
I bet eventually,
they won't even bother coming
to try clothes on.
They will
do everything online without leaving home.
Exactly...
If it can be done online,
why not do it online?
Come on,
let me propose another toast
to our friendship!
Cheers!
Tianji,
use
the pitcher.
Come on, I'm a lightweight.
Don't...
Cheers.
What have you been up to lately?
Come on, eat up.
Playing video games.
Come on, my old classmate.
Let's
have a drink.
Aren't you the one
who played a role
in the "Flower Fairy" back then? Wang...
Yep...
Wang Xiaoyong.
Yes, I'm Wang Xiaoyong.
Wang Xiaoyong from Class 8.
Long time no see.
We really should
have the girls from back then
come and see.
The prince has turned into a toad.
They just called him a toad back then.
Have you heard that?
Cao Xin is now
the boss of Bolly Fashion Group.
Cao Xin is a boss now?
Impressive!
No, that's not true.
I'm just an operations manager
in charge
of the group's regional operations.
No matter what, you're still
some sort of an executive, right?
-Yeah.
-Exactly.
In just 2 years, Cao Xin
went straight
from assistant to an executive.
I always knew
you had it in you.
Out of all our classes,
I knew you'd make your mark.
As for Qi Shi,
she hasn't amounted to much.
Don't even bring her up.
What's wrong with Qi Shi?
Wasn't Qi Shi
on par with you in school?
But now,
she can only sell clothes
at a street stall
and support
her brother, who got out of jail.
Her whole family is dirt-poor now.
Yeah...
Their family
is indeed drowning in debt.
Indeed.
I didn't even dare to say hi
when I ran into her
on the street last time.
I was afraid
she'd ask me to lend her money.
I just saw her on the overpass
the other day.
At her stall, right?
Yeah.
Didn't I just say that
studying was useless?
Exactly.
What's up?
What is wrong with you guys?
Qi Shi sets up a stall
and sells clothes to earn her living.
What's wrong with that?
Does that make her any inferior?
Besides,
did the Qis ever ask you
to lend them money?
Did they?
And look at you guys!
Back in school,
you copied Qi Shi's homework
and sucked up to her every day!
Now you're talking behind her back.
Listen,
we're all classmates.
If you can't have any empathy,
at least have some conscience!
Hey, what's wrong with Cao Xin?
I think there's something wrong with you!
Well...
Mom.
This month's allowance
for you.
They say children you raise
will look out for you when you're old.
I guess this is what it means.
We are lucky.
Yes, of course.
If I remember correctly,
we have two kids, huh?
Mom,
my store just got quite a lot of clothes
for middle-aged and elderly people.
You can pick whatever you like
when you visit.
I'm not old yet.
Who wants
those middle-aged and elderly styles?
I quite like
the dress for young people
you picked
for me last time.
Fine.
You can still pick whatever you like.
They're just sitting there anyway.
Well,
you said you were going to attend
some investment event last time.
Just the one Cao Xin introduced to you.
How did it go?
How was it?
It was so unreliable, as he was the one
who introduced it to me.
They are a big company.
We are out of their league.
But Mom, Dad, don't worry.
I've already figured out a way.
I don't need big companies
or big brands to help.
Our little store can make it on our own.
What way?
It's a secret.
Miss,
could you please fill out a questionnaire?
I'm doing a survey for my clothing store.
Miss,
could you please fill out a questionnaire?
Hello,
could you...
No.
Excuse me, miss,
could you please fill out a questionnaire?
Thank you, miss.
Have a nice day.
Is what our daughter
is doing really going to work?
She hasn't
given out many all morning.
No worries.
Our daughter
has a head for business.
Didn't she say that?
She needs to do market research first
before she makes steady strides.
Miss,
could you fill out a questionnaire?
I don't want the pancake.
I'm going there for buns
with marinated leaf mustard filling.
Their buns are delicious.
Are they really that good?
Yeah.
You'll want more after you eat some.
Want more after you eat some?
Could they have
added something suspicious to them?
No.
They're so good.
I'm heading out for a bit.
Oh, God!
Which jerk did this?
Who did this?
I'll deliver them
to the construction site later.
The workers there are impatient
and blunt.
You can't handle them.
Okay.
Save a portion
for our daughter.
I already did.
They're all in this foam box.
Call them over
to eat later.
Ride carefully on your way.
Take it slow.
Okay, I got it.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah!
Big buns!
Big buns for sale!
Steaming hot big buns!
Sir.
How many do you want?
Two with marinated leaf mustard filling.
Sweetie, you're done?
Go sit there and eat.
Your mom just left
and saved a portion for you.
Business must be good.
I wouldn't have any
if you didn't save some for me.
Come on, eat them while they're still hot.
It's okay.
Why did you get so many cuts?
It's nothing.
It's much easier
than mining coal.
I'm happy with it.
You really know how
to make the best of a bad situation.
And you know what?
Don't underestimate our little stall
or
our small cart.
It may be a small business,
but we make pretty good money.
Really.
Dad,
I'm your daughter.
You...
You don't have to brag to me.
Why would I brag to you?
Why would I brag to my daughter?
You know what?
We may have few customers
right now,
but those in the neighborhood,
at that construction site,
and
in those office buildings
all call
to order buns at mealtime.
Your mom and I take turns delivering them,
and we still can't keep up.
I'm not bragging to you.
Look, another call.
Hello?
Where do you live?
Unit 3, Building 6?
Okay, okay, I'll deliver them right away.
Nowadays, everyone is busy
with no time to come downstairs.
We should just be diligent,
take phone orders,
and deliver to their doors.
So, Sweetie,
to do business, you need
to open your mind
and be flexible like me.
As long as you're capable,
you can just make it anywhere.
Dad,
I think I've opened my mind.
What you just said
gives me so much confidence
in opening my online store.
Really?
When I make money,
I'll give you a big red envelope.
What? What did you say?
I said this big bun was really delicious.
Eat more if you think it's delicious.
I'm going to deliver buns.
Collecting scrap!
Xuanyu, Doudou.
Alright, you two should take a break.
-Here we go.
-Have some fruit.
The little prince is here.
Come on, my dear Doudou.
Would you like some fruit?
Look, which one do you want?
Which one?
Come on, let me get it for you.
Let Mommy get it for you.
Is it yummy?
Tell Mommy to have one, too,
huh?
Here, honey.
Honey,
can I discuss something with you?
Honey.
Haven't I always been thinking about
doing business with a friend of mine?
I'm short on principal right now.
I've carefully looked into the business.
It'll surely make profits.
Who are you going to do business with?
Still that blondie.
I missed out on
his foreign trade business
in Russia, right?
Right now, Russia literally
abounds with gold
for us to collect.
This time,
I almost talked my head off
before he agreed to count me in.
If there really were such a great thing,
would the chance fall on you?
Besides,
that blondie is not a good person.
You should stay away from him.
That's prejudice.
Just because he dyed his hair blond
doesn't mean he's a bad person.
Do you know
what he's like now?
He used to do shady things before
and once gave Dad a hard time on purpose.
His IQ is low,
and his character is even worse.
No way.
That must be a misunderstanding.
Don't just listen to Dad's side
of the story.
What do you mean
by "Dad's side of the story"?
There's no way Dad lied to me.
I don't agree.
Stop bringing up your dad all the time.
I'm already doing you
a huge favor
by letting
your old father live here.
Don't go too far.
Let's get up.
Anyway,
do not touch the family's money
and stop looking for suspicious shortcuts.
I'm back!
What's this smell?
What do you think it is?
Durian.
Come on, come and eat.
Dad,
how did you know I've been
craving this for so long?
I know you well!
Here, give it a try.
You know me best, Dad.
I went to several places before I
finally bought this.
How does it taste?
It's so good.
The windows.
Si.
Sit down.
I already opened the windows.
I know.
I know Zhou Xuanyu
doesn't like this smell.
Doudou doesn't like it either,
taking after his dad.
Dad, you have some, too.
-Okay, I'll have some.
-It's delicious.
Si.
I'd like
to discuss something with you.
What is it? Go ahead.
Your grandpa has been
living in the countryside
for the past few years.
Lately,
he's been calling me frequently,
saying that
he feels very, very lonely out there,
with no one to chat with.
Your grandpa is getting old,
and I'm worried about him.
I'm thinking
of bringing him here
just to live with us.
No problem!
Anytime. Even the bed is ready.
That's what I want
to discuss with you.
I've decided that your grandpa and I
will go live with Cao Xin.
Cao Xin is a grown man,
but he doesn't know how
to take care of himself.
I'll go over and help him out.
After your grandpa stays for a while,
if he's not used to it,
I'll go back to the countryside with him.
We'll just rent a house there
and
settle down.
Dad, you don't
have to go to all this trouble.
I know.
I know you're a good child
and care about your family.
Since you were little,
you've always cared about others
and put others first.
You'd rather hurt yourself
than let others suffer.
But there has to be a limit.
Si,
you chose
to keep living with Xuanyu,
and I support you.
However,
if I keep living here,
and if your grandpa also
moves in to live here,
Zhou Xuanyu's resentment
will definitely keep growing.
This way, I'd be causing you
too much trouble
instead of supporting you.
Dad.
Please don't say that.
You've never caused me
any trouble.
And Grandpa certainly hasn't either.
Do you know
how reassuring it's been having you
here at my place the past two years?
You can't bear to leave me behind,
can you?
And Doudou!
If Doudou knows you're leaving,
he'll surely be so sad.
Silly girl,
I'm not leaving.
I'm just moving
into Cao Xin's place.
You two live so close to each other.
In the future,
just call me anytime
if you need anything.
I'll come over right away.
If you want me to take care of Doudou,
just drop him off anytime.
I'll look after him for you anytime.
Is that good?
Dad.
Si,
you're a mother
yourself now.
You must understand my decision.
[All the Rage]
Hey, is this place really okay?
[Warehouse for Rent]
It's several miles away
from downtown.
On our way here,
I didn't see
a single person in sight
It's so deserted.
Here.
It's better with no one around.
The quiet environment and cheap rent
make it a perfect spot
for running an online store.
Be careful.
This works.
I hereby declare
that my shop has officially entered
the internet era
of All the Rage 2.0.
Great!
I'll make it!
Go for it! Good luck!
Bro,
wait a minute.
Hold on.
Bro,
don't worry.
Trust me.
I'll get the money for you right away.
Also,
don't forget the shares you promised me.
Make sure you keep them for me.
I'm counting on you
to make a killing this time.
Okay,
wait for my updates.
Good night, bro.
All right.
Give it to me. Give me that.
Honey, listen to me, honey.
This really is
a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
We're going to make a fortune soon.
We will strike it rich.
I knew you couldn't do
any decent business with that blondie.
Honey.
-Give it to me.
-Trust me, honey.
Honey, I'm begging you.
Zhou Xuanyu,
can you sober up?
Get real.
Who doesn't want to make money?
Everyone earns money
step by step.
Why do you keep dreaming
about getting rich
overnight?
Do you think this is realistic?
What do you mean?
I'm your husband.
I'm earning bread for our family.
And you're jinxing it
like this?
You're hopeless.
Get out of the way.
Anyway, I'm telling you,
I can get rich!
I have the capability to get rich!
Come back.
Get out of my way!
I got it.
You've always looked down
on me, haven't you?
No matter what I do,
I'm nowhere near as good
as your ex-boyfriend,
who was an ex-con, right?
Stop talking nonsense!
I'm talking nonsense?
Do you know how much
I've sacrificed
for you and our family?
Do you know how much pressure
I'm under?
I've borrowed every penny I could.
Are you hoping to see me fall,
so you can run with Qi Zhi?
I'm not...
I'm not!
Listen carefully.
I'm bent on doing this business.
Nobody is going to stop me
from getting rich!
You know?
Dad, Mom, stop arguing.
You're just like your mother,
always siding with outsiders!
Dad.
Son.
Son. What's wrong, son?
Let Dad check in on you.
Let me check.
Let me see...
Taxi.
We're going to the hospital.
To the hospital.
Si! Si!
Si...
Si!
Trust me!
I will definitely get rich!
I definitely can!
I definitely can...
I can do it.
Dongfang.
Dongfang!
Yes, Dad?
My right eye has been
twitching all night.
Is something bad going to happen?
Dad,
this is pure superstition.
Nothing's going to happen.
No,
something must've gone wrong.
Hello?
Si,
what are you doing?
Where's Doudou?
Doudou is asleep.
I'm watching TV.
It's a bit loud.
Mom, it hurts.
What was that sound?
What's wrong with Doudou?
It's fine.
He just accidentally
bumped into the corner of the table.
Nothing serious.
Is he okay?
Don't worry.
Who was Grandpa on the phone with?
Your sister.
He kept saying he had a bad feeling
and was worried that something
might have happened to Si.
No, Si was crying.
Something must have happened.
Go over to Si's place to see
if anything happened
and keep us updated.
Okay, I'm heading over now.
C-Call me anytime
if there's anything wrong.
Don't worry, Dad.
Grandpa, it'll be fine.
Okay.
You can't take this lying down.
I'll settle
this score with Zhou Xuanyu
later.
You didn't tell Dad and Grandpa, did you?
Nope.
Grandpa's eyelid kept twitching.
I told him you were fine,
so he could sleep at ease.
I'm your older sister,
but I still make you worry.
Don't say that.
What's your plan now?
I'll find a place
for you to stay in a while.